

# TRINH PHAM

# DIGITAL EXPERIENCE DESIGNER

#### **PROFILE**

Trinh Pham is a multidisciplinary designer who focuses on the methodology and principles of both UX/UI design and motion graphics animation.

With her ability to explore and "consume" new creative solutions and technology, she is able to combine her compassion and love for design and illustrations to create immersive and meaningful experiences for others

Oakville, Ontario



+1 6479077545



trinhboni@gmail.com

#### **EXPERIENCES**

# Freelance Designer | MAY 2017 - PRESENT

Working as a contractor doing various design work (mostly ux/ui, branding and motion) for different clients and companies.

# Internship at Forge Media + Design | MAY 2018 - SEPT 2018

I joined the Interactive Team as a UX/UI + motion graphic designer. I was responsible for helping out with any graphic design, building mockups/ prototypes, production, execution as needed.

# Internship at WebTV Asia | JUNE 2017 - SEPT 2017

Worked at Web TVAsia (a leading Digital entertainment company) in Vietnam as a Motion Graphic Designer. Ability to work with variety projects with the main production and design team of the company.

#### UX Researcher For Sunlife Financial | AUG 2017 - DEC 2017

We did multiple user usability testings and analyzed datas to help enhance the user experience on the Sunlife website.

#### **EDUCATION**

**Bachelor Of Interaction Design** 

SEPTEMBER 2015 - 2019 SHERIDAN COLLEGE

#### **SKILLS**

Adobe Suite CINEMA 4D

UX / UI Design Sketch

HTML / CSS Illustration

#### SOCIAL

(O) /trinhphamdesign/

in /trinh-pham-aa5959135

/TrinhBonBon

# **PORTFOLIO**

trinhphamdesign.com